

Julia Lima

UX Designer

Auckland, New Zealand **Phone:** +64 27 511 3958

Email: julia.lima.dg@gmail.com **Web Portfolio:** julialima.com.ar **LinkedIn:** linkedin.com/in/limajulia Reliable, well-organised, professional and constantly seeking to improve. UX designer with two years experience in a software company. Excellent at solving problems creatively and quickly. Interested in growing as a person and as a professional permanently, looking for permanent feedback.

Skills & Tools

Ideation
Wireframing
User Research
Visual Design
Interaction Design
Responsive Design
Documentation

Sketch (Wireframing)
InVision (Prototyping)
CSS/HTML (Web Development &
Prototyping)
Typeform (User Research)
Heap (Data Analysis)

Education & Certifications

BACHELOR IN DESIGN - MINOR: GRAPHIC Universidad Provincial de Córdoba Argentina

DEVELOPMENT AND DESIGN OF WEB PAGES Universidad Tecnológica Nacional Córdoba - Argentina

USER RESEARCH - METHODS AND BEST PRACTICES
Interaction Design Foundation

UX DESIGN ACCELERATE Academy Xi Melbourne - Australia

Work Experience

FERGUS SOFTWARE LTD.

Position: UX Designer. Jan 2018 - Present. Auckland, New Zealand

Job management software for trades businesses. It's main objective is to help business owner from quoting to invoicing a job. New Zealand's leading trade job management solution with 1500 users.

GRUPO PROYECTAR

Position: Product Designer - Freelance & Co-founder. Aug 2017 - Present. Argentina & remote

A mobile and web applications to control home-care services efficiency by monitoring health professionals activity. Currently used by aproximately 1000 users (between medical professionals and admin people).

TURÍSTICOS

Position: Product Designer - Freelance and Co-founder. 2016 - 2018. Argentina & remote

An e-commerce web application developed with a tourism expert and a computer engineer. Its purpose is to sell entretainments, activities and trips to tourists at local level. Nowadays it is being used in two cities of Argentina by aproximately 200 users.

GNOME OUTREACH PROGRAM FOR WOMAN

Position: UI Designer - Intern. Dec 2014 - Feb 2015. Remote Internship project for a US company called Evergreen that needed to migrate its desktop application to a web one. My task was to create the style guide for this new web app.